(Amy:)I know your present is...
(Amy:)for us to be intimate tonight.
(Sheldon:)I see.
(Sheldon:)Is that all right?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry,
but this is a litigious society.
(Sheldon:)I'm gonna need verbal consent.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)You know what, let me pull a
quick contract off the Internet.
So, if you don't like Star
Wars, why are you here?
(Wil:)Oh, I'm just having fun.
Everyone takes Star
Wars so seriously.
(Wil:)Like if the movie's bad,
it's gonna ruin their lives.
(Raj:)Is it bad?
Did you hear something?
(Raj:)Oh, my God. It's bad.
Somebody kill me.
(Wil:)See? That's
what I mean.
(Wil:)When you wake up in the
morning, whether this is
(Wil:)the greatest movie ever
or a total piece of crap,
(Wil:)your life isn't
gonna change at all.
(Howard:)He's right.